Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards State Legislative papers, Inclusive: 1957-1991, Bulk: 1982-1990.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- 70th Session, 1977-1990; 5
  - Topical, 1977-1990; 6
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Prison Site Selection, 1987-1988 (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Disability, 1987 (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Drug Abuse, Governor’s Task Force, 1987 August (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Dallas County, Dallas Legislative Programs, 1986-1987 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Dallas County, Duncanville and DeSoto Chambers of Commerce, 1986 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Dallas County, Grants, 1985-1986 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Dallas County, Resolutions, 1985-1986 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Dallas County, Various District Information and Projects, 1986-1987 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Education, General, 1987 (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Education, Management Training, Dimensions of Effective Leadership, 1987 (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Education, Management Training, Information, 1987-1988 (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Education, Management Training, LEAD Advisory Council, 1987-1988 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Education, Management Training, LEAD Advisory Council Meeting, 1988 (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Education, Management Training, LEAD Program Information, 1987, undated (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Education, Management Training, Leadership Development, 1985-1988 (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Education, Management Training, Leadership Development Training, 1986-1987 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Education, Management Training, Texas LEAD Center, 1988 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Education, Management Training, Texas LEAD Center (1 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Education, Management Training, Texas LEAD Center (2 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Elderly and Aging, Weatherization, undated (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Election, Presidential Primary, Research and Speech Notes, 1987 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Election, Primary, Texas 2-S.T.E.P. Notes, 1987 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Election, Primary Voting Analysis, 1987, undated (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Ellis County, Resolutions, 1986-1987 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Ellis County, Various District Information, 1986-1987 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Ellis County, Invitations, 1986-1987 (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Employee Leasing, 1987 (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - Farm Bureau/Ag Fund, 1987 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - Freestone County, Various District Information, 1985-1987 (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - Gamefowl, 1987 (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - General, 1986-1990 (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - General, Notes and Schedules, 1987, undated (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, Boardroom Meetings, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, Information and Articles, 1987 (Box 158, Folder 19)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, Medical Liability (1 of 2), 1986-1987, undated (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, Medical Liability (2 of 2), 1986-1987, undated (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, Medical Regulation and Discipline, 1987 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, Reports and Articles, 1986-1987 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, Reports, Articles, and Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, Rules and Regulations, 1982-1987 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Health, Child Abuse, Mental Health and Human Services, 1986-1987 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Health, Long-Term Care, Elderly Rights, 1987 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Health, Long-Term Care, Rules and Standards, 1985-1987 (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Health, Malpractice Statistical Reports, Board of Medical Examiners, 1987 (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Health, Medicaid, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Health, Medical Examiners Licensing Bonds, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Health, Medical Malpractice, Notes and Information, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Health, Medical Malpractice Report, 1986 February (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Health, Rural Medical Education Board Statistical Report, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Health, Texas Drug Reps, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Health and Human Services, General, 1985-1987 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Health and Medical, 1977, undated (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Henderson County, Various District Information, 1985-1987 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, 70th Session Strategy, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Alternatives for Revitalizing and Diversifying the Economy, Booklet, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, American Electronics Association, 1986-1987 (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Business Development and Jobs Creation Task Force, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - High Technology, Education: UT Austin, 1984-1987 (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - High Technology, Federal Agencies and Commissions, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, Federal Research Money, 1986-1987 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, General, 1984-1987 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, General, 1985-1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, General, 1986-1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, General, 1987, undated (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, IC2 Institute, UT Austin, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, International Informatics Access ‘87, 1986-1987 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Location and Industrial Research, Booklet, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Problems, 1984-1987 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Problems: Massachusetts, 1982-1984 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs, 1984-1986 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, Research Funding, undated (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, Select Committee on Higher Education, 1986-1987 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, Select Committee on Higher Education, 1987 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Southern Growth Policies Board, 1984-1987 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Supercollider (SSC), 1987 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Supercollider Articles, 1987-1988 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Supercollider Opposition, 1987, undated (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Texas Computer Industry Council, 1987 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Texas Economic Development Commission (TEDC), 1984-1987 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Texas Learning Technology Group, 1987 (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, Texas Science and Technology Council, 1986-1987 (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Texas Senate Space Science Industry Commission, 1988 (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - High Technology, Texas Innovation Information Network System (TIINS) and Bill Summaries, 1987-1990 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, Universities, 1983-1986 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, University of Texas at Arlington Programs, 1984-1987 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, University of Texas at Austin Programs, 1977-1987 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, University of Texas System, 1987 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, Venture Capital, 1985-1987 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Highways and Transportation, Corsicana, 1987 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Hill County, Various District Information, 1984-1987 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Innovation and Economic Development, 1987, undated (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Insurance, 1987 (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Insurance, “A Call for Insurance Reform”, undated (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Insurance, Liability Insurance and Tort Reform, Analysis, 1986, undated (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Insurance, Liability Insurance and Tort Reform, Analysis, 1988-1989 (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Insurance, Liability Insurance and Tort Reform, Articles and Research, 1987, undated (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - Insurance, Liability Insurance and Tort Reform, Civil Justice League, 1987 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Insurance, Liability Insurance and Tort Reform, Testimonies and Research, 1986-1988 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Juvenile Justice, undated (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Labor, 1987 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Labor, AFL-CIO, Unemployment and Workers’ Compensation, 1987 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - League of Women Voters of Dallas, Legislative Priorities, 1987 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Local Measured Service, AARP, 1984-1987 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Local Measured Service, Advisory Group (1 of 2), 1985-1988 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Local Measured Service, Advisory Group (2 of 2), 1985-1988 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Local Measured Service, AT&T Deregulation News clippings, 1984-1987 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Local Measured Service, Bypass of the Local Exchange in Texas, undated (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Local Measured Service, Communications Workers of America, 1986-1987, undated (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Local Measured Service, General Information, 1983-1986 (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Local Measured Service, Public Utility Commission General, 1985, undated (Box 164, Folder 14)
    - Local Measured Service, Regional Contacts, 1987, undated (Box 164, Folder 15)
    - Local Measured Service, Silver Haired Legislature, 1986-1987 (Box 164, Folder 16)
    - Local Measured Service, Support for S.B. 46, 1985-1987 (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - Local Measured Service, Support Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 164, Folder 18)
    - Long-Term Care, Criminal Background Checks, S.B. 200 Signing, 1987-1988 (Box 164, Folder 19)
    - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1987 (Box 164, Folder 20)
    - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Healthcare, 1987 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Minorities in Engineering, Southwest Symposium (1 of 2), 1987 October 12-13 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Minorities in Engineering, Southwest Symposium (2 of 2), 1987 October 12-13 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Seatbelt Law, 1987 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Sex Offender Treatment, Interagency Council Annual Report, 1987 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Silver Haired Legislature, 1986-1988 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Southern Regional Primary, 1987 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, 1986-1988 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Speeches, 1987, undated (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - State Budget (1 of 2), 1986-1989 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - State Budget (2 of 2), 1986-1989 (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - State Property Tax Board Publications, 1987 (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Sunset Advisory Commission, Summary of Recommendations to the Governor and the 70th Legislature, 1987 February (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Supreme Court of Texas, State Commission on Judicial Conduct, Justice C.L. Ray, 1987 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Texas Campaign Finance Journal, 1987 September-November (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Texas Department of Community Affairs, 1985-1987 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Texas Department of Community Affairs, Community Services Block Grant, 1986 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Texas Growth Fund Related, 1987 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Texas Pride Speech, undated (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Tort Reform, Alliance for Legal Insurance Equity, 1986 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Tort Reform, Articles (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Tort Reform, Articles (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Tort Reform, Articles and Preliminary Bill Draft, 1986-1987 (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Tort Reform, Bills Information, 1987, undated (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Tort Reform, The Case for Tort Reform, undated (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Tort Reform, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Tort Reform, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Tort Reform, Joint Committee Report, 1987 January 22 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Tort Reform, Minority Report, 1987 January 27 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Tort Reform, Reports (1 of 3), 1987, undated (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Tort Reform, Reports (2 of 3), 1987, undated (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Tort Reform, Reports (3 of 3), 1987, undated (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Tort Reform, Reports and Recommendations, 1987 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Tort Reform, State Board of Insurance, 1986-1987 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Tort Reform, Statistics, 1986, undated (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Tort Reform, Texas Liability Insurance Closed Claim, 1987 February (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Tort Reform, Trial Lawyers Association Publications, 1986-1987 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Tort Reform, Tort Reform Articles (1 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Tort Reform, Tort Reform Articles (2 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Tort Reform, Conference, 1985 January 4 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Transportation, 1987 (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Trinity River Authority, 1987-1988 (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - Trucking Deregulation, 1987 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Tuition Equalization Grant Program Information, 1987 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Utilities, AT&T Deregulation (1 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Utilities, AT&T Deregulation (2 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Utilities, A&M Telecommunications Study, 1986-1987 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Utilities, Companies, 1984-1987 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Utilities, Deregulation Information (1 of 2), 1987, undated (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Utilities, Deregulation Information (2 of 2), 1987, undated (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Utilities, Equal Treatment of Long Distance Companies, 1987 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Utilities, Gas and Electric General, 1984-1987, undated (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Utilities, Local Exchange Telecommunications Act, Amendments and Information, S.B. 444, 1986-1987 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Utilities, Local Exchange Telecommunications Act, S.B. 444 Related Materials and Analysis (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Utilities, Local Exchange Telecommunications Act, S.B. 444 Related Materials and Analysis (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Utilities, Local Exchange Telecommunications Act, Substitutes and Amendments (1 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Utilities, Local Exchange Telecommunications Act, Substitutes and Amendments (2 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Utilities, Long Distance Service Information, 1987 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Utilities, MCI Telecommunications Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Utilities, Nuclear Power S.B. 1284, 1985-1988 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Utilities, Proposed PUC Rules (1 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Utilities, Proposed PUC Rules (2 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Utilities, S.B. 229 Telecommunications Carrier Regulations Amendments, 1987 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Utilities, S.B. 229 Utilities and Information, 1987 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Utilities, Telecommunications Carrier Regulations, S.B. 229, 1987 (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Utilities, Telecommunications Carrier Regulations, S.B. 229 Filibuster Information, 1987 (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Utilities, Telecommunications Rates, 1987-1989 (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Veterans, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Water Resources, Spanish Grant Water System, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Water Resources, Texas Water Commission, McGregor, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Women, 1985-1987 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - Administrative, 1986-1988; 7
    - Chet Edwards’s 70th Session Legislation, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - District 9 Master List of County Projects, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Edwards’s Legislation, undated (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Elderly and Aging, Session Legislative Issues, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Interim Report to the 70th Legislature, Committee on Judiciary, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Legislative Conference, 1987 March (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Legislative Package, City of Houston, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Major Issues of the 70th Legislature, 1987 October (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Potential Legislation, 1987-1988 (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - Senate Committee on Nominations, Samples and Procedures, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Session Legislation, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Session Wrap-Up File, Chet Edwards (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 171, Folder 16)
    - Session Wrap-Up File, Chet Edwards (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 171, Folder 17)
- 71st Session, 1957-1991; 6
  This series holds papers from the 71st Legislature, 1989-1990, Edwards’s last session in the Texas Senate. It contains the subseries: Correspondence, Senate Bills, Senate Resolutions, House Bills, House Resolutions, Topical, and Administrative. A few topics of importance among these subseries are abortion, education, Medicaid, taxes, and especially workers’ compensation. The Administrative subseries refers to materials related to administrative tasks, session wrap-ups and summaries, potential legislation, appointments, columns, press releases, and newsletters, or various materials that relate to the legislative session as a whole.
  - Correspondence, 1988-1990; 1
    - Abortion (1 of 4), 1989-1990 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Abortion (2 of 4), 1989-1990 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Abortion (3 of 4), 1989-1990 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Abortion (4 of 4), 1989-1990 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture, 1989-1990 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Air Quality, 1989-1990 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - AIDS, 1989-1990 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Alcohol, 1988-1990 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Animal Cruelty, 1989 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Apartments, 1989 (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Appointments and Nominations, 1988-1990 (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Architect Licensing, 1989 (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Armed Forces, 1988-1990 (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - Arts, 1988-1990 (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - Audiology, 1989 (Box 172, Folder 15)
    - Bail Bonds, 1989 (Box 172, Folder 16)
    - Banking, Foreclosure, 1989 (Box 172, Folder 17)
    - Banking, 1988-1989 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Bill Requests, 1988-1990 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Bingo, 1989 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Bookkeeping, 1989 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Border Control, 1989 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Brazos River Authority, 1989-1990 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Building Construction, 1989 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Business, General, 1988-1989 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Business, Solicitations, 1988-1990 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - Campaigns, 1988-1989 (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - Certified Public Accountants (CPA), 1989 (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Children, CASA Appropriations, 1989 (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Children, Child Abuse, 1988-1989 (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Children, Child Care, 1989 (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - Children, Child Support, 1988-1989 (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Children, Foster Care, 1988-1989 (Box 173, Folder 16)
    - Cigarette Smoking Restrictions, 1989 (Box 173, Folder 17)
    - Cock Fighting, 1988-1989 (Box 173, Folder 18)
    - Commerce, 1988-1990 (Box 173, Folder 19)
    - Comptroller, 1990 (Box 173, Folder 20)
    - Computers, 1988-1989 (Box 173, Folder 21)
    - Congratulations (1 of 2), 1987-1990 (Box 173, Folder 22)
    - Congratulations (2 of 2), 1987-1990 (Box 173, Folder 23)
    - Copyright, 1988 (Box 173, Folder 24)
    - Court, 1989 (Box 173, Folder 25)
    - Credit Unions, 1989 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Crime Victim’s Rights, 1988 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Criminal Justice, General (1 of 3), 1988-1990 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Criminal Justice, General (2 of 3), 1988-1990 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Criminal Justice, General (3 of 3), 1988-1990 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Criminal Justice, Jury Trial, 1989 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Criminal Justice, Prisons, 1989-1990 (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Crop Insurance, 1988-1989 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Dallas County, 1988-1989 (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Deceptive Trade Practices Act, 1989 (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Department of Human Services, 1988-1990 (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - Disability, 1989-1990 (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - Education, Career Ladder, 1989 (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - Education, Corporal Punishment, 1989 (Box 174, Folder 14)
    - Education, Dropouts, 1988-1989 (Box 174, Folder 15)
    - Education, Equal Access, 1989 (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - Education, General (1 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 174, Folder 17)
    - Education, General (2 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 174, Folder 18)
    - Education, Funding, 1988-1989 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Education, Higher Education (1 of 3), 1988-1990 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Education, Higher Education (2 of 3), 1988-1990 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Education, Higher Education (3 of 3), 1988-1990 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Education, Homeschooling, 1987-1989 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Education, Public School Funding (1 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Education, Public School Funding (2 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Education, Sex Education, 1989 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Education, Southwest Conference, 1990 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Education, Special Education, 1989-1990 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Education, State Schools Tuition Credit, 1989-1990 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Education, Student/ Teacher Ratio, 1989-1990 (Box 175, Folder 12)
    - Education, TASP Test, 1990 (Box 175, Folder 13)
    - Education, Teachers, 1989 (Box 175, Folder 14)
    - Education, Teacher Pay Raise (1 of 3), 1987-1989 (Box 175, Folder 15)
    - Education, Teacher Pay Raise (2 of 3), 1987-1989 (Box 175, Folder 16)
    - Education, Teacher Pay Raise (3 of 3), 1987-1989 (Box 175, Folder 17)
    - Education, Teacher Retirement (1 of 3), 1988-1990 (Box 175, Folder 18)
    - Education, Teacher Retirement (2 of 3), 1988-1990 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Education, Teacher Retirement (3 of 3), 1988-1990 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Education, Transportation, Natural Gas, 1989 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Education, Tuition Equalization Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Education, Vocational Education, 1989-1990 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Elderly and Aging, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Electric Cooperative Act, 1989 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Ellis County, 1988-1990 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - Emergency Services, undated (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Employment, 1989-1990 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Employment, Texas Employment, 1989-1990 (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Engineering, 1989 (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - English Only, 1987-1989 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Environment, 1988-1990 (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - Equal Employment, 1987-1990 (Box 176, Folder 15)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1988-1990 (Box 176, Folder 16)
    - Film, 1989 (Box 176, Folder 17)
    - Fire Ants, 1989-1990 (Box 176, Folder 18)
    - Fishing, 1989 (Box 176, Folder 19)
    - Flag Burning, 1989-1990 (Box 176, Folder 20)
    - Flag Requests, 1988-1990 (Box 176, Folder 21)
    - Food Stamps, 1990 (Box 176, Folder 22)
    - Forestry, 1989-1990 (Box 176, Folder 23)
    - Funeral Service Industry, 1990 (Box 176, Folder 24)
    - Gas, 1989 (Box 176, Folder 25)
    - General (1 of 8), 1987-1990 (Box 176, Folder 26)
    - General (2 of 8), 1987-1990 (Box 176, Folder 27)
    - General (3 of 8), 1987-1990 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - General (4 of 8), 1987-1990 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - General (5 of 8), 1987-1990 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - General (6 of 8), 1987-1990 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - General (7 of 8), 1987-1990 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - General (8 of 8), 1987-1990 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Governor’s Office, 1987-1989 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Guardianship, 1989 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Gun Control (1 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Gun Control (2 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Gun Control (3 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Hazardous Duty Pay, 1989-1990 (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - Hazardous Waste, 1989 (Box 177, Folder 13)
    - Health, Acupuncture, 1989 (Box 177, Folder 14)
    - Health, General, 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 15)